About

HTML

JavaScript

Adobe Suite

Evporionco

I am a software developer with a focus in web applications, front and back-end. I have a knack for troubleshooting and debugging and am not afraid to think outside the box to find solutions for tough problems. My background in fields outside of software gives me a leg up on my competition because of my eye for design and my experience in client-facing roles.



BRIAN WARD

WEB DEVELOPER

1545 Patton Circle, Apt C

Boulder, Colorado

cell: 626-773-6901

brianwardcs@gmail.com

github: bward3

INTERESTS

Computer Vision
Photography
Ultimate Frisbee
Esports

Experience	
DU Coding Bootcamp	 2022 - PRESENT
Boulder, CO	
Developed mastery in full-stack web-development by creating new web-based applications weekly	
Collaborated via Git with other developers in the program to create large-scale projects using free web APIs	
Hyatt Place Boulder	2021-2021
Boulder, CO	 2021-2021
Served guests upon arrival. Gained experience interacting directly and professionally with clients	
Freelance Editor	
Hollywood, CA & Boulder, CO	 2019 - 2021
Edited video projects based on clients' desires.	
Honed expertise in design, photography/ videography, and post-production. Became familiar with full Adobe suite	
Lead Teaching Assistant	
New London, CT	2015 2010
Ran tutor sessions for a number of computer science classes including: Algorithms, Data Structures, Computer Vision, Intro to Python	 2015 - 2018
Organized events for the computer science department, working closely with professors and classmates alike	
Education	
Connecticut College	 2014 - 2018
New London, Connecticut	
BA in Computer Science, Mathematics	
Awarded Senior Computer Science	
Award upon graduation	
Polytechnic School	 2010 - 2014
Pasadena, CA	
Expertise	

Node.js

CSS

Java